We've seen that you can control the behavior of
我们发现你可以通过指定滤波数量和每个滤波的大小
a convolutional layer by specifying the number of filters and the size of each filter.
控制一个卷积层的行为
For instance, to increase the number of nodes in a convolutional layer,
例如为了增加卷积层中节点的数量
you could increase the number of filters.
你可以增加滤波的数量
To increase the size of the detected patterns,
为了增加检测模式的大小
you could increase the size of your filter.
你可以增加每个滤波的大小
But there are even more hyper parameters that you can tune.
不过 还有许多你可以调优的超参数
One of these hyper parameters is referred to as the stride of the convolution.
其中一个是卷积的步长
The stride is just the amount by which the filter slides over the image.
步长是指滤波在图像的滑动量
In the example in the previous video, the stride was one.
在前一个视频的例子中 步长为 1
And we moved the convolution window horizontally and vertically across the image,
然后我们从水平和垂直方向把卷积窗滑过图形
one pixel at a time.
每次 1 像素
A stride of one makes the convolutional layer
步长为 1 使卷积层的
roughly the same width and height as the input image.
宽和高与输入图像大致相同
In this animation, we've drawn the purple convolutional layer as stacked feature maps.
在这个动画中 我们把卷积层涂成紫色 作为叠加的特征图
If we instead make the stride equal to two,
如果我们让步长等于 2
the convolutional layer is about half of the width and height of the image.
卷积层的宽和高约是图形的一半
I say roughly because it depends on what you do at the edge of your image.
我之所以说约是一半 因为这取决于你对图像边缘的处理
To see how the treatment of the edges will matter,
为了明白边缘处理的作用
consider our toy example of a five-by-five grayscale image.
考虑我们玩具例子中 5*5 的灰度图像
Say, we have a different filter now with the height and width of two.
例如我们这里是不同的滤波 高和宽为 2
Say, the stride is also two.
步长也为 2
Then as before, we start with the filter in the top left corner of
那么与之前一样 我们首先从图像左上角的滤波开始
the image and calculate the value for the first node and the convolutional layer.
计算第一个节点和卷积层的值
We then move the filter two units to the right and do the same.
然后我们向右移动滤波两个单位 进行相同操作
But when we move the filter two more units to the right,
不过当我们向右移动滤波两个单位时
the filter extends outside the image. What do we do now?
滤波超出了图像 现在我们要怎么办呢？
Do we still want to keep the corresponding convolutional node?
我们是否仍然要保持相应的卷积节点呢？
For now, let's just populate the places where the filter
目前为止 我们只是在滤波超出的地方填入问号
extends outside with a question mark and proceed as planned.
然后继续按计划进行
So now, how do we deal with these nodes where the filter extended outside the image?
那么我们怎样处理滤波超出图像部分的这些节点呢？
We could, as a first option,
第一种做法是 我们可以
just get rid of them.
删除它们
Note that if we choose this option,
注意 如果我们这样做
it's possible that our convolutional layer has
我们卷积层可能没有
no information about some regions of the image.
图像部分区域的信息
This is the case here for the right and bottom edges of the image.
这个例子中是图像的右侧和底部边缘
As a second option,
第二种做法是
we could plan ahead for this case by padding the image with
在这个例子中 我们可以提前对这个图形零填充
zeros to give the filter more space to move.
让滤波有更多空间可以移动
Now when we populate the convolutional layer,
现在我们添加卷积层时
we get contributions from every region in the image.
得到图像每个区域的贡献
We can specify which option we'd like to be
我们可以通过为卷积层设置填充
the case by setting what's known as the padding for our convolutional layer.
指定我们想要的选项
If you prefer the first case where you're okay with
如果你倾向于第一种情况
potentially losing some nodes in the convolutional layer,
认为失去卷积层的一些节点没有问题
you'll set your padding to valid.
可以设置填充为有效 (valid)
On the other hand,
另一方面
if you prefer the second case,
如果你倾向于第二种情况
you'll set your padding to same.
可以设置填充为相同 (same)
In the next lesson,
在下节课中
we'll show you how to pass these arguments into Keras
我们会向你展示 调优卷积网络时
when tuning your convolutional network.
怎样把这些参数值传递到 Keras 中